<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Trainings on AEB - PD Portfolio</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/appendices/trainings/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Trainings on AEB - PD Portfolio</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:1313/appendices/trainings/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Advisory Skills Training</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/appendices/trainings/advisory-skills-training/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/appendices/trainings/advisory-skills-training/</guid>
      <description>Summary In this advising training session, we looked at the ideas and theories that support good communication and advice-giving. We talked about how important it is to take into account a number of variables when providing advice, such as self-awareness, knowing the client&amp;rsquo;s needs, and making sure communication is clear and efficient (Purdue University, n.d.). In order to guarantee the quality and acceptance of advice, we looked at possible communication risks and strategies to avoid them.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Conflict Management Training</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/appendices/trainings/conflict-management-training/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/appendices/trainings/conflict-management-training/</guid>
      <description>Summary We studied the framework of productive conflict management during this training, focusing on crucial phases for successful resolution (Rossingol, 2023):&#xA;Opening: Outlining the purpose of the meeting, establishing shared objectives, gauging willingness to solve problems, and developing a schedule. Investigation: Paying attention, examining concepts and objectives, converting grievances into possible remedies, and maintaining focus on the ultimate objective. Negotiation: coming up with potential solutions, reaching agreements to stop future disputes, and clearly recording agreements through documentation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cross-Cultural Management Training</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/appendices/trainings/cross-cultural-management-training/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/appendices/trainings/cross-cultural-management-training/</guid>
      <description>Summary: With insights from Bono&amp;rsquo;s Six Thinking Hats model and Hofstede&amp;rsquo;s three levels of mental programming (human nature, culture, and personality), this training presented a thorough examination of cross-cultural interactions. We explored the importance of cultural awareness in today&amp;rsquo;s globalised world, realising the influence of culture on human behaviour and attitudes. We looked at how international teams are shaped by globalisation and multiculturalism, highlighting both opportunities and challenges, with an emphasis on internationalisation (Hofstede, n.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Group Dynamics Training</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/appendices/trainings/group-dynamics-training/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/appendices/trainings/group-dynamics-training/</guid>
      <description>Summary This training session was very informal, we spend it with Evgenya talking about challenges within our team - specifically with Rupina who wasn’t coming to classes or doing her parts of the assignment. We expressed our frustrations and worries about her productivity, lack of participation and what that means for us. The coach recommended we talk to her, express our feelings and give her a warning. Based on theory, this would’ve been our groups storming phase (keka, n.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Leadership Styles Training</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/appendices/trainings/leadership-style-training/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/appendices/trainings/leadership-style-training/</guid>
      <description>Summary: During the training we discussed the various types of leadership that Goleman has described. Those are according to (Sinek, n.d.):&#xA;Visionary - inspiring, “come with me and you will do fine”; Affiliative - trust, connection, team spirit, conflict management, “first the people, task second”; Democratic - motivation, support, giving space, seeking consensus, “lets do it together”; Pacesetting - performance oriented, “do it my way”; Coaching - combo of democratic and strategic, encourage, challange, feedback, ”let me help you”; Commanding - no employee input, controlled.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Negotiation Training</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/appendices/trainings/negotiation-training/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/appendices/trainings/negotiation-training/</guid>
      <description>Summary: We looked at the complex field of negotiation during the training. We studied the 4-stage and 8-stage frameworks and examined negotiation as a dynamic process (Cole, 2024). We discovered the importance of the exploration and bidding stages and how they help produce outcomes that benefit both parties (Cole, 2024). We also talked about how to improve the effectiveness of negotiations through the use of research from psychology and communication studies in our strategic questioning techniques.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
