<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Main Body on Inholland University of Applied Sciences - The Hague - International Creative Business - Class 2B - 2024.06.03 - Graded by Evgenia Gontsarova</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/main/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Main Body on Inholland University of Applied Sciences - The Hague - International Creative Business - Class 2B - 2024.06.03 - Graded by Evgenia Gontsarova</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:1313/main/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Personal Growth Plan</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/main/personal-growth-plan/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/main/personal-growth-plan/</guid>
      <description>Professional attitude: This term I will attend all classes prepared and show enthusiasm for projects. By the end of the term I will not have any missing parts of the assignments and not have any retakes. I will achieve this by setting deadlines for assignments and dedicating an hour everyday minimum to do them.&#xA;Collaborations: By the end of this term me and my team will have found a way to work smoothly together and hold each other accountable.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Three Day Work Placement</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/main/three-day-work-placement/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/main/three-day-work-placement/</guid>
      <description>My goal is to learn what it’s like to work in an office environment in a team of people when organizing a marketing campaign. Action plan: During my three day work placement I will collaborate with the marketing department at Litpersona to create marketing plan for expansion into Greenland. My goals are to write three posts for their facebook account and three advertisements that they can run on facebook. After that, I need to communicate with graphic designer on what sort of visuals those posts and ads need.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Internship and Minor Plan for Year 3</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/main/internship-plan-year-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/main/internship-plan-year-3/</guid>
      <description>In year 3, I will start my year in Utrecht Hogeschool doing an international advertising minor. My objectives there are branding strategy, cultural values and communication in an international perspective, creative research, psychology of marketing communication and a final creative assignment. I also plan to develop my leadership skills, widen my network of connections and step out of my comfort zone by going to a different university in another city alone.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Most Recent CV</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/main/most-recent-cv/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/main/most-recent-cv/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
