<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Intervisions on Inholland University of Applied Sciences - The Hague - International Creative Business - Class 2B - 2024.06.03 - Graded by Evgenia Gontsarova</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/appendices/intervisions/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Intervisions on Inholland University of Applied Sciences - The Hague - International Creative Business - Class 2B - 2024.06.03 - Graded by Evgenia Gontsarova</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:1313/appendices/intervisions/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>1.2 Intervision 1 for Term 1</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/appendices/intervisions/intervision-1-term-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/appendices/intervisions/intervision-1-term-1/</guid>
      <description>Question chosen: Rupina’s - “how could she manage time to less affect the groups work flow?”&#xA;Background questions for her: How do you manage your time right now? What stands in your way to do assignments by our set deadlines? What kind of accommodations would make sure you do your parts before deadlines?&#xA;Key words of the problem: Overwhelming Stress Chaos Procrastination Lack of motivation&#xA;Advices: Set timers for 30 minutes and keep adding another 30 minutes after one goes off.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1.3 Intervision 2 for Term 1</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/appendices/intervisions/intervision-2-term-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/appendices/intervisions/intervision-2-term-1/</guid>
      <description>Question chosen: Maxim’s “How can I efficiently navigate a situation where I&amp;rsquo;ve engaged a freelancer for a project task, yet I&amp;rsquo;m uncertain about our budget allocation from the client?”&#xA;Explanation: The question shows Maxim&amp;rsquo;s worry regarding the efficient administration of a freelancer-led project, considering the unpredictability of project budget and schedule. Maxim is concerned about: Communication with freelancer: Maxim has engaged a freelancer to complete a project task, but he is uncertain if the client&amp;rsquo;s budget will allow for the freelancer&amp;rsquo;s fees.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1.4 Intervision 3 for Term 1</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/appendices/intervisions/intervision-3-term-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/appendices/intervisions/intervision-3-term-1/</guid>
      <description>Question chosen: Mine “How can I better manage my time to fit in work, school, hobbies and social life without sacrifising quality of each?”&#xA;Question Explanation: My aim to successfully manage several significant facets of my life is reflected in the question. Time management: To make the most of my free time, I want to effectively plan and arrange my tasks. Work, School, Hobbies, and Social Life: I want to succeed in all of these areas, and they all demand my attention and dedication.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>1.5 Intervision 4 for Term 1</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/appendices/intervisions/intervision-4-term-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/appendices/intervisions/intervision-4-term-1/</guid>
      <description>Question chosen: Hamza’s “How can we effectively navigate moments of tension and uncertainty during the ideation phase to generate ideas and transform them into a coherent concept?”&#xA;Question Explanation: How can tension and uncertainty be managed during the idea generation stage to produce concepts that are meaningful and clear? In order to guarantee that original ideas can be developed into a coherent project concept, Hamza is looking for solutions for handling problems like conflicts or ambiguity that frequently occur during creative brainstorming.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
