<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Challenge Journals on Inholland University of Applied Sciences - The Hague - International Creative Business - Class 2B - 2024.06.03 - Graded by Evgenia Gontsarova</title>
    <link>/appendices/challenge-journals/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Challenge Journals on Inholland University of Applied Sciences - The Hague - International Creative Business - Class 2B - 2024.06.03 - Graded by Evgenia Gontsarova</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/appendices/challenge-journals/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>1. Challenge journal Term 1</title>
      <link>/appendices/challenge-journals/challenge-journal-term-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/appendices/challenge-journals/challenge-journal-term-1/</guid>
      <description>Challenge: Managing time for work, school, hobbies and social life to minimize stress without sacrificing quality of either.&#xA;WHICH ACTIVITIES HAVE YOU ATTEMPTED AND HOW DID THE EXECUTION GO? What was worthwhile? What did you discover? What surprised you? Which insights were new? I tried scheduling out my days in hours, maximising my productivity. For example if I know I have my workout class at 12 - I wake up at 8 and do my work until its time to leave at 11, then on my way there and back I also do some small tasks such as replying to comments/messages.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2. Challenge journal Term 2</title>
      <link>/appendices/challenge-journals/challenge-journal-term-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/appendices/challenge-journals/challenge-journal-term-2/</guid>
      <description>CHALLANGE: Lack of initiative and work ethic from other students which leads to group’s work being delayed, causes a lot of stress and uncertainty.&#xA;WHICH ACTIVITIES HAVE YOU ATTEMPTED AND HOW DID THE EXECUTION GO? What was worthwhile? What did you discover? What surprised you? Which insights were new? I attempted to talk to that team mate, raising my concerns. It was met with acknowledgement of the problem but refusal to adjust behaviour.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3. Challenge journal Term 3</title>
      <link>/appendices/challenge-journals/challenge-journal-term-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/appendices/challenge-journals/challenge-journal-term-3/</guid>
      <description>CHALLANGE: Uncertainty about the assignment and how to meet high quality demands without an example before deadline.&#xA;WHICH ACTIVITIES HAVE YOU ATTEMPTED AND HOW DID THE EXECUTION GO? What was worthwhile? What did you discover? What surprised you? Which insights were new? I have attempted to reach out to coaches get feedback from them on done parts. I have tried aiming for the good grade but for me its hard to accomplish within the strict word count.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>4. Challenge journal Term 4</title>
      <link>/appendices/challenge-journals/challenge-journal-term-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/appendices/challenge-journals/challenge-journal-term-4/</guid>
      <description>CHALLANGE: Struggling to keep up with personal development portfolio, export plan, financial plan, export research and prepare for the financial exam as well as get good grades in all. This is made harder with the distraction of good spring weather.&#xA;WHICH ACTIVITIES HAVE YOU ATTEMPTED AND HOW DID THE EXECUTION GO? What was worthwhile? What did you discover? What surprised you? Which insights were new? I tried dedicating full days for just one of the reports, I tried doing one task for every report everyday, I tried dedicating afternoons to school work and morning for work and personal hobbies, tried doing assignments in the line of deadlines but nothing really sticks or works to the extend for it to become a go to method.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
